sluggerotoole.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy « Slugger O'Toole

Slugger O’Toole Limited (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.  This privacy policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us and it should be read in conjunction with our Website Legal Notice.

  1. We may collect and process the following data about you: 
    1. Information that you provide by registering at, posting, commenting or otherwise interacting on our site [http://www.sluggerotoole.com](http://www.sluggerotoole.com/) and any _(and all predecessor and related websites)_ (our “Site”).
    2. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
    3. Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, other communication data, and the materials that you access.
  2. We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
  3. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us: 
    1. To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
    2. To recognise you when you return to our site.
  4. We may use your personal information for communicating with you about our Site and any related services.  We will not pass your information to a third party for any commercial reason.
  5. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.
  6. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.
  7. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
  8. We may disclose your personal data to third parties: 
    1. If Slugger O’Toole Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
    2. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Slugger O’Toole Limited, our customers, or others.
  9. The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access personal data held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
  10. Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.
  11. Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to us [via this spam-proof e-mail link](http://scr.im/slgradmin).  

Last modified 19 April 2010
